She's here.
Dead Bride is a horror, thriller film directed by Francesco Picone.
After her father’s death, Alyson, her partner Richard and
their baby return to her childhood home.
Following a few shocking supernatural events, Alyson discovers that she and her family have been living
with a terrible curse, unleashed in the past by a bride killed by Alyson’s grandfather.
Soon after Alyson’s child disappears and she has no choice but to embark on a frightening journey into
the underworld, to free herself from the bride’s curse and to look for her daughter.
Alyson, played by Jennifer Mischiati.
Richard, played by Christoph Hülsen.
Dave, played by Douglas Dean.
Father Elbert, played by Seán James Sutton.
Nelson, played by Michael Segal.
Corpse Bride (also known as Tim Burton's Corpse Bride) is a 2005 stop-motion animated musical Gothic fantasy film
directed by Mike Johnson and Tim Burton and written by John August, Caroline Thompson, and Pamela Pettler.
Set in an English village, Corpse Bride stars Johnny Depp as the voice of
Victor, while Helena Bonham Carter voices Emily, the title character.
An international co-production between the United States and United Kingdom, produced by Tim
Burton Productions and Laika Entertainment, and distributed by Warner Bros.
Pictures, Corpse Bride is the first stop-motion feature film directed by Burton after previously
producing The Nightmare Before Christmas (1993) and James and the Giant Peach (1996).
Corpse Bride drew inspiration from a 17th-century Jewish folktale, which Joe Ranft
introduced to Burton while they were finishing The Nightmare Before Christmas.
Work on the film started in November 2003 while Burton was wrapping up Big Fish.
His next live-action feature, Charlie and the Chocolate Factory,
was produced simultaneously with Corpse Bride.
Production of the stop-motion animation feature took
place at 3 Mills Studios in London.
It was shot with Canon EOS-1D Mark II digital SLRs, rather than the 35
mm film cameras used for The Nightmare Before Christmas.
Burton immediately brought regular collaborators
Depp, Carter and Danny Elfman aboard.
Corpse Bride is dedicated to executive producer Ranft, who
died a month before the film's release.
Corpse Bride premiered at the 62nd Venice International Film Festival on September
7, 2005, and was released in theaters on September 23 in the U.S.
and on October 13 in the U.K.
to critical and commercial success.
The film was nominated for Best Animated Feature at the 78th Academy Awards.
The film explores themes of supernatural, bride, childhood home, cursed.
The tone is dark and intense.